freeplant.net 2016-10-21

# Free Fruit Seeds - Totally Free

**Privacy Policy**  
www.freeplant.net is committed to protecting your privacy when you visit our Web site. ww.freeplant.net does not collect personal information about individuals, such as names and mailing or e-mail addresses, unless it is knowingly provided by the individual and he or she has agreed to the terms under which Totally Free Stuff will use it. 

**Disclosure of Information**  
www.freeplant.net will not sell, trade, or rent your personal information to others. We do not automatically log personal data nor do we link information automatically logged by other means with personal data about specific individuals. We may use IP addresses to compile and provide aggregate statistics about our visitors, traffic patterns, and administer the site. This statistical information may also be related to third parties, but these statistics will not include any personally identifying information, track user’s movement, and gather broad demographic information for aggregate use. IP addresses are not linked to personally identifiable information. We collect only the personal data that you may volunteer while using our services. We do not collect information about our visitors from other sources, such as public records or bodies, or private organizations. 

**Our Commitment to Children's Privacy**  
Protecting the privacy of the very young is important to us. For that reason, we do not collect or maintain information at our sites from those we actually know are under 18, and no part of our site is structured to attract anyone under 18. 

**External Web Sites**  
Please note that www.freeplant.netcontains links to other web sites. Please be aware that we are not responsible for the privacy practices of these other sites. We encourage our users to be aware that when they leave our site that you read the privacy statements of each web site that might collect personally identifying information. 

This privacy statement applies solely to information collected by www.freeplant.net. If you have any questions or concerns about our privacy policy, please contact: info@freeplant.net
